http://www.hymnary.org/info/privacy.html

Skip to main content
In the first 11 months of 2020, we had 6.99 million users from 237 countries around the globe access this Hymnary website! We are so grateful to be able to provide timeless hymns from the ages to all who find them a blessing, and we are so thankful to all who support us with gifts of time, talent and treasure.
If you feel moved to support our work today with a gift of any amount and a word of encouragement, we would be grateful.
To donate online, please use the Calvin University secure giving site. If you'd like to make a gift by check, please send it to: Hymnary.org, Calvin University, 3201 Burton Street SE, Grand Rapids, MI 49546.
What though my joys and comfort die?
The Lord my savior liveth.
What though the darkness gather round?
Songs in the night he giveth.
(My Life Flows On In Endless Song)
Click here to donate to Hymnary.orgI have already donated. Please don't show this to me again this fund drive
Home Page
Home Page
User LinksLog in
Register
Discover
Browse Resources
TextsTunesInstancesPeopleHymnals
Exploration Tools
About Us
CollectionsMy Starred HymnsMy FlexScoresMy HymnalsMy Purchased FilesStore
Connect
Blog
Forums
Volunteer
Facebook
Twitter
Close Menu
Log inRegister
Search
Advanced Search
Search by Melody
CollectionsMy Starred HymnsMy FlexScoresMy HymnalsMy Purchased Files
Discover
Browse Resources
TextsTunesInstancesPeopleHymnals
Exploration Tools
Topics
Popular Texts
Popular Tunes
Lectionary
Store
Blog
Forums
Tutorials
About Us
Privacy Policy
Because we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it, we have adopted this Privacy Policy. There are several Hymnary services that require the collection of information from you. These services include signing up with a user name and password to enable you to access community features. Other services may set cookies on your computer.
Our Use of "Cookies"
Cookies are small bits of data that we send to your computer. They identify you as a Hymnary user and contain information regarding your Hymnary preferences.
The cookies are not used for tracking users outside the Hymnary Web site, and they are not accessible by third parties.
Web Site Traffic Information
When you visit this or any Web site, information is available to the site on the pages you view, the time of your visit, the browser you are using, the address of the computer you visit from, and the address of the page you are coming from. We use this information internally only, to better understand user needs and preferences and make the Hymnary more useful. We do not share this information with third parties unless required by law, and we do not track Web sites you visit before or after you access the Hymnary.
Our Use and Disclosure of Information
The Hymnary will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties.
Notification of Changes
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to Hymnary or as we incorporate suggestions from our users.
The Hymnary is not responsible for notifying users of changes to this policy.
We will post the amended Privacy Policy promptly on our Web site so that you can always review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the Hymnary Web site at hymnary.org/info/privacy.html for the current version of our Privacy Policy.
About | Copyright | Privacy | Contact us | Advertise with us | Publisher Partnerships | Give | Subscribe
It looks like you are using an ad-blocker. Ad revenue helps keep us running.
Please consider white-listing Hymnary.org or subscribing
to eliminate ads entirely and help support Hymnary.org.
